Mataram
so friends today I am going to tell you about a hidden software
which you get
on many Windows 10 and Windows 11
and believe me brother it has been around for
more than a year since I started using it and
what is it brother I mean a lot of personal
PC users maybe you guys use it on your PC right now
tell me in the comments are you still using it or
not yes friend I am
talking about Windows Sandbox here
I had talked about it a long time ago but today I am going to do it
practically I will
say that brother even if I install a virus on it
then there is no effect on the PC
because friend it has been made for this work so let's take a
look out
how it works and
believe me brother if you are a PC user even if you use a normal
PC a little bit then according to
me you should definitely use it
because friend in today's time
you people believe that you can get a
virus through email not only virus you can use it
for any personal users also I
mean  It's a very powerful thing, let me take a look at
how it functions, you'll definitely
enjoy it, friend. Let's go on the
desktop and see for yourself. So let's begin the
video. Okay, friends, we've reached the desktop here.
First of all, brother, we have to
install it. It's simple, as mentioned before,
just write Windows Features here.
Okay, after writing this much, you will get this
option. Go into it. Okay, here
you have to look carefully. If you
scroll down a little,
you will find Windows
Sandbox. Okay, let me tell you one thing,
brother, Windows Sandbox
is available in the Pro version of Windows 10 or Windows
11. It is not available in the Home Edition. Now you
can say that this is a problem,
but for Windows Sandbox, you
can go to Pro because it is a very powerful feature.
And friend, I use it many times, that's why I'm
showing it to you. Now see,
you have enabled Sendbox from here. You will have to
restart the system once. Everything is not working.
Now you don't have to do anything else.
You simply if you
type Windows Sandbox in the search, look friend,
Windows Sandbox is found on the top and you press enter,
we have reached Windows
Sandbox, whatever Windows you have,
you will get that inbuilt one,
like I am using Windows 11, so
I will not get Windows 11 inside,
look friend, in a way you can say that I have done the
emulator type work and right
brother, you are seeing Windows 11 running on Windows 11, this will
remain with your 10 as well, if you look carefully, this is also
an operating system, everything will
run in it as it was running in your system, just
today you get some storage income and the rest of
it is a service for service, meaning you have to check any app, you have to
check any file, something like this on mail,
virus type thing or anything like that, if you want to
run any app related to you once at a time, then it is
good for that, I am showing you as an example,
see here, if I do it here,
then my browser will run quickly
inside it,  Look sir, you can simply
write 'obvious' here, it could be any application,
like I'm obs, let's download it, so I'll
write 'obvious' here, I'll
click on it and easily do everything very quickly
because there wo
n't be much on it, let's talk about your handbag,
because not much is running, so
many people use virtual box to
check different operating systems, Windows, I think
this is the best, and I use this and this
because all these
files from FireUS keep coming, so it's the best for that,
now look, I've simply installed it here, and that's
also it, now
what is this scene, I'm installing the Windows 11 inside, like this,
think for yourself, now
I can run it out here, similarly you
can check out any application,
first time here, look, I'll finish it,
and look, Obs will
start here, look sir, this has
started, it's running fine on the system,
due to which screen recording is happening  If you
run one inside, you
can check the application in this way and the most interesting
thing is that it won't take up much storage at all.
Like when you click on this cross,
all the things that you have downloaded in the machine,
whatever you have checked is completely
finished and out of memory. See, it is also being written,
everything will be permanently set, so click OK.
Everything will be set in this way. Basically, you
can do it. It is a very fine thing,
friend, if you do it correctly, friends, you will
agree that the software is really powerful, friend.
That is why we use it for so long.
My purpose is to check viruses,
but friend, you
can see by adding apps on it that many times it happens that
we don't have to use the app for long term, we
just have to check it quickly. And the
best thing in this is that when we cross it, brother, whatever
data was used, it will be saved permanently
daily, so nothing can be better than this. So,
according to me, friend,
you should not use Virtual Box when
you get this option inbuilt. Try it now and do
tell me what you feel, the rest is fine, friend.
If you like this video then you
can definitely like it, subscribe and share it, till then
bye friend Jai Hind Jai
Bharat Vande